# **YAXING SON**

Web Development Engineer

yaxingson@gmail.com











## Summary

My name is Anthony Fu, a master of computer science student and a freelance software engineer. My passion for software lies with dreaming up ideas and making them come true with elegant interfaces. I take great care in the experience, architecture, and code quality of the things I build.

## Projects

- Vitest: A blazing fast unit test framework powered by Vite. \* 10291
- Vitest: Presentation Slides for Developers. \* 8912
- Vitest: Collection of essential Vue Composition API utils.

### Work Experience

#### **NuxtLabs** Software Engineer

Sep 2021 - Present | Remote

- Integrated Vite into Nuxt 3 resulted in 50x faster development time.
- Authored `unplugin` unifing the API between Webpack and Vite.
- Created Vitest that improved the developer experience on testing.

#### **NuxtLabs** Software Engineer

Sep 2021 - Present | Remote

- Integrated Vite into Nuxt 3 resulted in 50x faster development time.
- Authored `unplugin` unifing the API between Webpack and Vite.
- Created Vitest that improved the developer experience on testing.

#### **NuxtLabs** Software Engineer

Sep 2021 - Present | Remote

- Integrated Vite into Nuxt 3 resulted in 50x faster development time.
- Authored `unplugin` unifing the API between Webpack and Vite.
- Created Vitest that improved the developer experience on testing.

#### Education

NuxtLabs Software EngineerSep 2021 - Present | Remote

## Skill Stacks

**Frontend** TypeScript, JavaScript, Vue, Nuxt, Vite

**Backend** Node, MongoDB, Sqlite, Serverless, Nginx, Docker

**DevOps** Firebase, AWS, Azure, AliCloud

## Awards

NuxtLabs Software EngineerSep 2021 - Present | Remote NuxtLabs Software EngineerSep 2021 - Present | Remote NuxtLabs Software EngineerSep 2021 - Present | Remote

## Languages

PDF Version
Last updated at August 2nd 2022, 6:39:57 am.